The White Countess is a drama, romance, war film directed by James Ivory.
In 1930s Shanghai, 'The White Countess' is both Sofia, a fallen member of the exiled Russian aristocracy, and a nightclub
created by a blind American diplomat who asks Sofia to be the centerpiece of the world he wants to create.
Todd Jackson, played by Ralph Fiennes.
Countess Sofia Belinskya, played by Natasha Richardson.
Matsuda, played by Hiroyuki Sanada.
Olga Belinskya, played by Lynn Redgrave.
Princess Vera Belinskya, played by Vanessa Redgrave.
Grushenka, played by Madeleine Potter.
The White Countess is a 2005 drama film directed by James Ivory and starring Ralph Fiennes, Natasha
Richardson, Vanessa Redgrave, Hiroyuki Sanada, Lynn Redgrave, Allan Corduner, and Madeleine Potter.
The screenplay by Kazuo Ishiguro focuses on a disparate group of displaced
persons attempting to survive in Shanghai in the late 1930s.
The film explores themes of shanghai, china, countess,
american abroad, air raid, nightclub owner.
The tone is emotional.